I know, I know, what you must do is train.
Eu sei, eu sei, é treinar que resta pra você.
The thing about gymnastics is that you release endorphins, do you understand?
O que há na ginástica é que você solta endorfinas, entendeu?
And that helps with stress relief, depression, among other things.
Isso é... diminui sua tensão e depressão.
I mean, gymnastics really help out in so many ways.
Em suma, a ginástica ajuda em muita coisa.
The thing is, when someone doesn't have the physical... attitude,
A questão é quando não se tem disposição... fisicamente,
when one doesn't have the willpower.
quando uma pessoa não possui a vontade.
Tell me where I can find it because if there's somewhere selling me
Diga-me onde posso encontrá-la, pois, se existe algum lugar que me venda
willpower or the right attitude towards training, going to the gym.
a vontade ou a disposição de praticar exercícios, de comparecer e treinar.
Oh my God, please tell me where it is because I just don't have it.
E Deus mio, digam-me onde, porque eu simplesmente não tenho.
I don't have it, I can't seem to find it, it's nowhere inside me.
Não a tenho, não consigo encontrá-la, ela não está em mim.
Wherever the hell I left it, assuming it exists since everyone says,
Não sei onde diabos ela está, caso exista, já que todo mundo diz,
You start off...
Você começa...
Once you get started with the gym, you always feel like doing more.
E após um tempo fazendo exercício físico, sempre quer mais.
It never happened to me before!
Isso nunca aconteceu comigo antes!
I hate it! I go to the gym, work out, and come back swearing. Do you understand me?
É terrível! Eu vou ao ginásio, faço exercícios e volto bravo. Entendeu?
Because sometimes, I just don't feel like going.
Pois ontem... eu nem tinha vontade de ir lá.
All I want to do is sit at home; I don't feel like working out.
Desejo simplesmente ficar em casa, sem vontade de fazer exercícios.
What am I supposed to do, sister?
O que devo fazer, manita?